i.jd.com 2018-11-27

# JD.com, Inc.

If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post an updated version on our Website (as defined below). Please review this policy from time to time. If you have any questions relating to the Privacy Policy, please contact us at contact@jd.com. 

#### Introduction

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose and safeguard your personal information in regards to the use of corporate.jd.com and related investment web pages and services (the "Website"). The security of your personal information is of utmost importance, so we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of all personal information you have provided to us and we take all reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from unauthorized use. We will also take efforts to comply with the applicable laws under which we process the information collected from you. By using and accessing this Website, you accept the practices described under this policy.

#### Collection of Personal Information

We may collect information about you when you visit this Website and use our services. Types of information that we may gather include:

  * __What you give us such as: name, email address, contact details, and, email communications if you request receipt of certain notifications and updates and/or if you contact us directly, and any other personal information disclosed when using our Website and services.
  * __Automatically collected information: When you visit this Website, enabling cookies on your browser allows us to collect information about you. This and other technical information collected is used to identify your browser to create a more personalized online experience. Cookies may be enabled to activate some of the features and functionality of this Website.
  * __Information from other third-party sources.

#### Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

Personal information that we collect from you will be used and disclosed only to provide services to you, or otherwise to carry out our business. Types of personal information we may use and disclose include:

  * __For internal purposes, to provide a service to you.
  * __For communications with you.
  * __For legal purposes and reasons: There may be some circumstances where we will be legally required to share personal information.

#### Externally

We may share your information with third parties we engage with to perform services on our behalf. However, we will not sell or loan your information to third parties unless we ask for your permission upfront.

#### Data Retention

We will retain your information as required to provide services to you and in compliance with our legal obligations.

We will ask for your consent before releasing information about you to third parties outside those stated above.

#### Security and Protection of your Personal Information

Our Website is secured and encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use. While we use industry-standards to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security of your personal information.

#### Children and Privacy

Our Website and services do not target and are not intended for users under the age of 18. We do not knowingly solicit personal information from users under the age of 18 or send them requests for personal information.

#### Third-Party Sites

Our Website may contain links to other websites operated by third-party companies. We do not share your personal information with those websites (unless we have asked for your permission as stated above) and are not responsible for their privacy practices.

We do not control or are not responsible for the privacy and security practices of any third-party companies. We encourage you to check the applicable privacy policy of the third-party website to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you.

#### Business Transitions

In the event that we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Website for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.
